Oh, but a fancy flying maneuver sends him sadly over Mashikaku.
It's only a matter of time before he catches up to torture.
Huh?
Here he comes.
They're gonna do something.
He's gonna let me.
How do you like that?
No way.
There you go.
Now keep it up, just like I said.
It's it!
Come on, go!
Seriously heated race into the final round.
Come on, you can do it!
Just a little further!
Man, this is great!
God.
What a moment!
Inspiring!
All right!
I'm up!
Usopp!
I'm coming!
Come, Luffy!
It's so fast!
Awesome!
I won't let you win!
Incredible!
Moments ago, Straw Hat Luffy couldn't even stand in his skates, much less stay in them.
And now he's neck and neck with Tiki Cheetah, who is powered up with his double speed full dash!
Oh crap, I taught him how to stand and skate, but not how to turn!
Straw Hat Luffy has once again left the course!
He is now disqualified from round three!
He knew it, he's hopeless!
The Speed King Tiki Cheetah continues the race with a four lap lead!
Long Nose, take my hand, hurry!
Whoa!
Historian Nico Robin uses a long whip to keep her team in the race!
Will it be enough to make up for lost time?
Damn it, that woman!
Don't worry, I'll handle it, Portia.
There it is!
Tiki Cheetah and his triple speed rocket dash!
Hey, aren't you paying attention?
He left the course, damn it!
The air is safe, the air is safe!
Coach Thopsi's angry complaint is overruled and shut down!
I have to do something before it's too late.
Mujiakarnete!
Oh no!
I try not to struggle, girl.
Got it?
The more you wiggle around, the more tangled you become.
I'm an invertebrate!
That does nothing to me!
Nice work, Juby!
That was nothing.
Oh no, that freak took out Robin!
Hey, Coach Lame Brain, if we don't do something about that Cheeky Cheetah guy in Quick, we're
gonna lose this race.
You don't need to remind me!
Wait, Cheeky Cheetah?
Cheetah?
That just might work.
Hey, you!
The old man with the horse, are you here?
Huh?
Uh, do you mean me?
Yeah, listen!
That long Kiwi you gave Luffy, where did you get that thing from?
What are you talking about?
Shut it!
Come on, old man, hurry!
Huh?
There, they grow in the branches of those trees.
All right, Shrubhead, bring back a branch of that tree!
Move it!
Hey, is that any way to ask for a favor?
Ah, look, it might be our only chance to stop that guy!
Now get going!
With a tree branch?
Yeah, you heard me!
Now hurry!
What the?
Hey, what's he doing?
Here, you can ride Shelly's.
Thanks, old man!
I don't know if this will work or not, but it's better than doing nothing.
Four minutes into the race and Cheeky Cheetah has an incredible 13-lap lead!
Now passing the four and a half minute mark and Cheeky Cheetah's lead has increased to 15 laps!
Things certainly aren't looking too good for the Straw Hat dangers!
Damn it, where is he?
There it is.
Four minutes and 50 seconds!
Ten more seconds and the Foxy Devils will clinch a shout-out victory!
I'm not gonna make it.
Only five seconds remain!
Wait, what's happening?
What is that?
What's going on down there?
What happened to Cheeky Cheetah?
Cheeky Cheetah left the course just before the end of the round and is disqualified!
What a stunning upset!
In a miraculous come from behind victory, round three goes to the Straw Hat dangers!
Cheeky Cheetah, no!
Cheeky Cheetah!
No!
But!
Hooray!
Come on!
But why?
What happened?
Cheeky Cheetah has special properties.
In some cases, these properties have been known to mesmerize cats, meaning the smell of
the plant itself is just like catnip.
Cheetahs are cats too.
I figured it was worth a shot.
I get it. So that's why he was sniffing all over Luffy before the race.
Probably so.
Impressive knowledge, Mr. Cook.
Oh, it was nothing, really.
We won that one by the skin of our teeth.
The Straw Hat Dangers have managed to score a point of their own,
but the Foxy Devils still have the advantage.
There's no time to bask in the afterglow of victory, though.
Round four will be starting soon.
The point-getters will be the historian Nico Robin
against the fishman Jubei.
We're in for a great race.
Listen, how to turn. First, you...
Don't worry. I got it.
What do you mean, you got it? You didn't have it a second ago.
Look, I did what you told me to do.
I watched how everyone else was skating. I'm ready.
Huh?
We know that he's going to use that stupid beam again.
Yeah, that do-do beam is going to be a problem.
Do-do beam?
Bloss!
Usopp, I've got an idea.
Huh? What is it?
You are so naughty!
Good idea, don't you think?
Ooh! Do I detect the brewing of an evil plan from the heartless and cruel Nami?
Her devious face is showing the complete-
Her face is devious!
Yours?
Round four is about to begin!
Long time no see.
Ready?
Goal!
Oh, no you don't.
I may not be as fast as Cheeky Cheetah, but I'm no slouch, either.
That's 20 seconds!
Defense, go!
Is... is he going to be able to do this?
All right!
Yes! Yes!
Way to go, Lupe!
Bring it on!
I'll be happy to give you another taste of my muchacaramente.
Oh, no you won't!
Whoa! Seems like he's getting the hang of it!
Straw hat movements and stupid flying!
Robin! Keep going! I'll handle this guy!
Right! Thanks!
Hey! My baton's gone!
Sorry!
What? Give me that back!
Don't even try. I'd just sit this one out if I were you.
Okay.
Astounding! The Straw Hat Rangers are on a roll!
They've just taken a one lap lead!
We'll see about that.
Hamburg, prepare for a full dash!
Right.
Usopp, it's time.
Yeah! Now, Operation Laugh and Fall.
Are you ready for this?
You know what?
It's time.
Yeah!
Now, Operation Laugh and Fall.
Are you ready for this?
You know it.
Hey, Split Head!
You gonna use your slow, slow dodo beam again?
Split Head!
Do-do-beam!
Don't make fun of him! He's handsome, intelligent, and wonderful!
Ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha!
Hey, Split Head!
You gonna use your slow, slow dodo beam again?
Ha-ha-ha!
Split Head! Do-do-beam!
Don't make fun of him!
He's handsome, intelligent, and wonderful!
Ha-ha-ha!
That stupid fox is anything but!
I'm serious about this!
I'm head over heels in love with him!
Impossible!
No one loves that crappy Split Head!
He added crappy to Split Head!
Handsome!
Split Head!
Split your pose!
You're happy!
Smart!
Nice!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Stupid Split Head!
You could de-
Nami, what are you doing?
You need to keep complimenting him!
But I can't!
It's making me sick to my stomach!
You think maybe we could switch up?
Insult me!
How dare you!
Uh...
But there is nothing to compliment!
It doesn't matter who says what!
Just keep repeating stuff!
Got it!
Split Head!
Manly!
It looks like the boss can't seem to fire his slow-slow beam!
A contradictory verbal assault by the stall-hats has brought him to his knees!
Time's almost up!
Ha-ha-ha!
Manly!
There you have it!
The Straw Hat dangers win round four by a landslide!
There will now be a five-minute break before the final round begins.
I can't believe I fell for that!
Nor did I expect this to drag out to another round.
Listen, we have to win the next one!
We'll use the you-know-what plan to seal our victory!
You got it.
Yeah!
Now, it's time for the final round of the event!
Both teams are at the starting line, ready to go!
But it seems that Girarin alone is representing the foxy devils!
The rest of the team is off the track!
Could this mean they're planning to use their most devious trick of all?
Devious trick?
Come on, you know it's just gonna be that stupid slow-slow beam again.
Oh, wow, you figured it out!
Yes, we're going to be using the slow-slow beam to stop your captain.
That's our little plan in its entirety.
Heh, not that you're gonna be able to do anything about it.
As if, weren't you paying attention to what happened in the last round?
Operation Laugh and Fall will stop him cold!
Hey, just skate like crazy, Luffy!
Yeah! Leave everything to me!
Okay, it's time to begin the final round!
Ready, go!
No, no! He's starting already!
Family! Family! Family! Family! Family! Family! Family! Family! Family!
Slow-slow beam!
There it is! An onslaught of slow-slow beams!
What's going on? Why isn't Operation Laugh and Fall working?
Eh-heh-heh-heh-heh-heh?
Were you to say something?
Airplugs! The straw half-dangers have been outsmarted!
That's our boss for ya!
Eh! We are screwed!
Uh, what the? Did he just deflect the slow-slow beam?
Oh, you noticed?
Yes, the slow-slow beam doesn't work on Gararine.
What? Really? No way! How is that possible?
Sorry, but it's a secret!
A secret? Oh, that makes perfect sense!
Ah, now I get it.
That's why the rest of your team wasn't on the course.
Yep!
This way, you can't hide from the beam behind any of the boxy devils.
Your whole team is gonna be turned into slow-pokes, but we won't!
This is bad! Now what are we gonna do?
20 seconds are up! Defenders go!
He-heh-heh-heh-heh-heh-heh! Time for you two to slow-down!
Luffy!
No!
Nami! A direct hit!
Navigator Nami and Sniper Usopp have fallen prey to the slow-slow beam!
Luffy! Behind you!
No way! Luffy has been stopped in his tracks!
Victory is now a near-sunday for the back of the devil!
He-heh-heh-heh-heh-heh! Now it's your turn!
There's no way I can dodge his attacks.
If I let that beam hit me, we're done for.
Only one thing to do...
Here, let's move a bit.
Aye-he-heh-heh-heh-heh-heh-heh-heh-heh, heuh-heh-heh-heh-heh-lops.
Heee-heh!
Oh, what's this?!
Niko-robin, who has been keeping the Straw Hat dangers in the game, has suddenly given up?
With only one minute remaining in the round, she has stepped off the course!
The effects of the slow, slow beam last for 30 seconds.
If Luffy can dodge the next attack, he'll still have a chance to win.
Failure is not an option.
I have to wait for just the right moment.
Robin, what are you doing?
If I'm over here with you two, I can avoid being hit by that beam, right?
Hmm? Yeah, but...
40 seconds remain, and Girarin has an easy three-lap lead!
What?
Think I'll give you two another dose just to be on the safe side.
Feed, feed, feed, feed, feed, feed...
Alright, Straw Hat Luffy, it's been a lot of fun, but now it's time to end this.
Feed, feed, feed, feed, feed...
Only 30 seconds remain!
If Straw Hat Luffy is hit with another beam, victory for the Foxy Devils is guaranteed!
Luffy!
This ends now!
Oh, crap!
Luffy, move it!
Get going!
Right!
20 seconds!
Mucha-kara!
So, how should I prepare you?
Grilled or deep-fried?
10 seconds left!
Straw Hat Luffy is moving at incredible speed!
These two are neck and neck now,
and it'll be a mad dash for the finish!
No!
You wouldn't!
The boss has slowed himself down!
Calm down!
Only five seconds left!
Those stalled blades won't work on me!
Huh?
Yeah!
The Strut Hat Danger's advantage of all of them
will come from behind the game!
Yeah!
We'll be right back.
Next, Wood Piece, screaming hot bombardment,
Pirate Dodgeball, I'm gonna be king of the pirates!